Guide to the Cornell Information Technologies records,1940-2009.
Cornell Information Technologies Records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Information Technologies records, 1940-2009.
16-13-3351
Cornell Information Technologies.
63.4 cubic feet.
Printed Materials, Publications, Reports, Research Materials,Correspondence
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, memos, meeting minutes, proposals, budget material, photographs, Project Ezra and Project Mandarin records, John Rudan's files and other records that document the history of computing at Cornell University.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
In 1966 the Cornell Computing Center and Machine Records were merged into the Office of Computer Services (OCS), and in 1970 the business systems group was split from OCS to form Management Systems and Analysis (MSA), which was merged back into OCS in 1978. In 1980 OCS became CCS, Cornell Computing Services, and in that decade was a partner with the Theory Center in creating and sustaining the Cornell National Supercomputer Facility. In 1988 the service organization became the Cornell Information Technologies, with the vice president's office, OIT, the Office of Information Technology, assuming responsibility for overall IT policy on campus.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, memos, meeting minutes, proposals, budget material, photographs, Project Ezra and Project Mandarin records, John Rudan's files and other records that document the history of computing at Cornell University.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell Information Technologies.; Rudan, John.; Cornell Information Technologies.; Cornell National Supercomputer Facility.; Cornell Theory Center.; Cornell University--Curricula.; Cornell University.Project Ezra.; Cornell University.Project Mandarin.; Cornell University.Division of Management Systems and Analysis.Office of Institutional Information.; Cornell University.Computing Center.; Cornell University.Office of Computer Services.
Subjects:
Information storage and retrieval systems.; Computers--Study and teaching.; Information science--Study and teaching.; Computer literacy.; Computers.; Computer software.; Computer-assisted instruction.; Educational technology.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Additional material and digital versions can be found online here: http://ecommons.cornell.edu/handle/1813/82
CONTAINER LIST
- IPA Fact Book, 1978-01 (Box 1)
- Institutional Planning and Analysis Reports (Box 1)
  - Interpreting Economic Indicators (S. Slovacek, J. Showacre, W. Schuette), 1979-07
  - Future Enrollments and Demographic Trends, 1978-04
  - Administrative Organization Analysis (Jack Lowe, B Davis), 1978-06-20
  - Employee Attitude - (SEAS Report) (T. Firtak, S. Slovacek), 1978-07
  - Alternative Contexts for Planning Cornell's Future (Ian Stewart), 1977-12-22
  - Analysis of Academic and Administrative Expense and Cost Trends - Endowed Units at Ithaca: 1967-1978 (B. Davis and S. A. Lawrence), 1978-12
  - Student Retention at Cornell - A Cohort Survivability Study, Institutional Information J. Boyce, 1977-04
  - Statistical Profile James Showacre, 1981-01
  - Undergraduate Financial Aid (S. Slovacek and B. Davis), 1978-08
  - Working Paper - Institutional Planning Process; A Rationale and Proposed Program for Cornell (Ian R. Stewart), 1977-06
  - Cornell University Budget Planning 1980-81 (John W. Rudan), 1979-07
  - A Quantitative Technique for Predicting Investment Results (Wade Schuette), 1979-10
  - An Overview of Administrative Information at Cornell (Wade Schuette), 1980-01
- Memo from Wade Schuette to JWR - Faculty Flow Modeling, 1978-03 (Box 1)
- Publications and Newsletters (Box 1)
  - Edunet News, 1984
  - Educom Bulletins, 1980 - 1986
  - IBM Perspectives in Computing, 1980-1982
  - IBM Information Processing, 1982, 1986
  - IBM Data Processor, 1981
  - CAUSE, 1988
  - The NCHEMS Newsletter, 1981, 1983
  - AIR Newsletter, 1981
  - EFPM Newsletter, 1982
  - Xerox, 1982
- TABLET - The personal computer in the year 2000 -Comm ACM, 1988-06 (Box 1)
- SPIRES Software demise, 1989 (Box 1)
- Facilities Management Services by CIT, 1989 (Box 1)
- VAX5 Issues (also regarding vax 1-4), 1990 (Box 1)
- SAS PC Project, 1989 (Box 1)
- Review of Administrative Computing (Russell S. Vaught), 1983-09 (Box 1)
- CIT Services Announcements, 1989 (Box 1)
  MOS, Macs, NEXT systems, CMS, Rates, Bitnet and others
- PROBLEM System Reference Manual v2.0 (A. Hanushevsky), 1989 (Box 1)
- PROBMACS (Writer's Ref; Macro Writer's Ref) (A. Hanushevsky), 1990 (Box 1)
- The Internet Worm Program: An Analysis, 1988 (Box 1)
  Purdue Tech Report CSD-TR-823
- Stalking the Wily Hacker (Clifford Stoll - Comm ACM), 1988-05 (Box 1)
- Columbia University - Presidential Task Force on Info Processing -Final Report, 1984-04 (Box 1)
- CHRISP - Cornell Human Resources Information System/Payroll, 1989-12 (Box 1)
  Design Review Document - Distributed Access/Electronic Approval
- Macterminal by DCS - using the Mac for access to mainframes, 1985-09 (Box 1)
- The Cost of Research at Cornell (Richard Schuler), 1987-07 (Box 1)
- Role of VM in future computing environments (R D Cowles), 1989-09 (Box 1)
- Cornell Theory Center - Parallel Push, 1989 (Box 1)
- OCS Announcements (Saved by J. W. Rudan), 1974-1979 (Box 1)
  (includes the HASP Special Announcement from 1971)
- CCS Announcements, Bulletins (Saved by J. W. Rudan), 1983-1988 (Box 1)
- Observations in Statistical Computing v2/#2 and assorted Technical Memorandum on Statistical packages, etc, 1983-1987 (Box 1)
- Graphics Services, etc in CCS - Mainframes to Micros, 1983-1987 (Box 1)
- CCS Computer Rate Sheets and Commentaries, 1982-1986 (Box 1)
- CCS - Cornell Computer Services Directory/Services, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
- Apple University Consortium, 1984-1988 (Box 2)
- Apple University Consortium - Campus Visits, 1984 (Box 2)
- CCS Retreat Packet (Box 2)
- Reorganization - CCS changes to CIT, 1988 (Box 2)
- CCS Accounting Billing System-Preliminary Docs and Specs, 1983 (Box 2)
- CCS Conceptual Design - CCS Accounting and Reporting System, 1984 (Box 2)
- CCS Computer Accounting and Billing System, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
- AT and T Information Systems, 1985 (Box 2)
- PC Sales Stats, 1984-1986 (Box 2)
- Monthly PC Sales Stats, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
- Weekly PC Sales Stats, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
- Monthly PC Sales Stats, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
- PC Sales Stats, 1987 (Box 2)
- PC Sales Stats, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
- PC Sales Analyses, 1987 (Box 2)
- PC Sales Analyses Vendor x Clients, 1984-1987 (Box 2)
- PC Sales Analyses by Vendor, 1984-1987 (Box 2)
- Macademia Slides, 1987 (Box 2)
- Macademia, Boston MA, 1987-05 (Box 2)
- AUC Conference, Data for Promotion Talk, 1986 (Box 2)
- Apple ReSellers Conference/Boston JWR Presentation Slides, 1986 (Box 2)
- Apple University Consortium (AUC )Meeting-to Stuart Lynn, 1988-04 (Box 2)
- Muggers' Monthly, 1986-03-1988-08 (Box 2)
- Stanford Documents License for SU-Mac/IP, 1988 (Box 2)
- CIS Leasing Corp. contract documents, 1979 (Box 2)
- CIS Contract Termination documents, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
- Disaster Recovery, 1988-03 (Box 2)
- VS2 Design Project, 1974 (Box 3)
- APL, 1974-1976 (Box 3)
- ASAP, 1969-1973 (Box 3)
- AUTOFLOW, 1969 (Box 3)
- CPS, 1971-1973 (Box 3)
- Ad Hoc Sub-Committee on Data Security, 1975 (Box 3)
- Administrative Systems Advisory Board, 1971-1975 (Box 3)
- AMPEX, 1970 (Box 3)
- CALS/CAG, 1980 (Box 3)
- Data Security, Integrity, and Privacy, 1973-1975 (Box 3)
- CIS, 1979-1984 (Box 3)
- DATEL CORP, 1969-1975 (Box 3)
- EDUCOM, 1976 (Box 3)
- EDUCOM, 1977-1980 (Box 3)
- EDUNET, 1978-1978 (Box 3)
- EDUNET, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
- Experimental IT, 1973-1975 (Box 3)
- Area II Computing Committee, 1973 (Box 4)
- Coordinating Area II, 1972 (Box 4)
- Area II Coord. Committee/Computing, 1974 (Box 4)
- Binghamton Regional (Cornell Cooperation), 1972-1976 (Box 4)
- Hamilton College, 1974 (Box 4)
- Ithaca College Regional, 1974 (Box 4)
- IBM, 1971 (Box 4)
- IBM, 1970 (Box 4)
- IBM General, 1966-1969 (Box 4)
- IBM, 1972-77 (Box 4)
- IMS Software, 1973-1974 (Box 4)
- Ithaca High School, 1976 (Box 4)
- Insurance, 1969-1977 (Box 4)
- Library Project, 1966-1970 (Box 4)
- 1604 Sale, 1964-1969 (Box 4)
- Mass Spec Sysytem, 1976 (Box 4)
- Computer Inventory, 1978 (Box 4)
- Campus Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 4)
- Mark IV, 1972-1976 (Box 4)
- Misc. Software, 1975 (Box 4)
- MSA, 1972-1976 (Box 4)
- OCS Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 5)
- Budget Planning/ Capital Plans, 1977-1983 (Box 5)
- Model 20 Project/Conversion, 1974-1977 (Box 5)
- Flexible Pricing of Computer Services (Seymour Smidt, Cornell University), 1967 (Box 5)
- Acronyms for SHARE 49 (Cecilia Uren later Cowles), 1977 (Box 5)
  The list of Smilie Faces 1991
- Recommendation to Increase Computing Capacity at OCS, 1973-07 (Box 5)
- EFPM Extension (further development), 1978 (Box 5)
- OCS Policies and Procedures Manual, 1974-06 (Box 5)
- The Crisis and Challenge of Administrative Data Processing at CU (Henry G. Vaughan), 1971-03 (Box 5)
- Towards Improving Information Systems at Cornell University (Henry G. Vaughan), 1974-04 (Box 5)
  A Feasibility Study and Plan
- Use of the Computer at Cornell - prior to MSA, 1973 (Box 5)
- Outlook for Administrative Teleprocessing at Cornell, 1973 (Box 5)
- Admin Data Processing at CU: Crisis and Challenge, 1971 (Box 5)
- Admin Data Entry at CU, 1975 (Box 5)
- The Future of Administrative Computing at Cornell (J A. Campbell), 1973-02 (Box 5)
  Prepared for the University Computing Board
- CIT Newsletters, 1988-11-1989-12 (Box 60)
  CIT News and Cornell Information Technologies Newsletters are in collection ARP 1364
- Ad Hoc Security Sub-Committee Security, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
  - Minutes/Position Papers
  - Legal and Legislative Issues - local and national
  - Proposed Cornell Policies
- Annotated Bibliography of Info Systems at CU - Selected Documents, 1975 (Box 5)
- Working Papers re Current Thinking on University MIS Concepts and Cornell's Current Status (H. G. Vaughan), 1976-07 (Box 5)
- Mgmt Systems Development and Student Info Processing by MSA, 1972-07 (Box 5)
- Info Systems Plans/Proposals by Rudan and others, 1978-1979 (Box 5)
- TYPIST Manual v2 (Herb Weiner and Paul Reilly), 1970-1979 (Box 5)
  Based on v1 by Elder with help from Blomgren, Maxwell, Morgan
- VM Issues (R D Cowles), 1974-1975 (Box 5)
- Review of Cornell Payroll/Personnel System (Legrady/Strauss Sandor Legrady and Howard Strauss from Princeton University), 1973 (Box 5)
  Commentary by Ed Hollenbeck, Stuart Comber, SAL, and P/P system work flows studies by R. N. Teague, Jr in 1972
- Report of the Advisory Comm on Financial Planning (Cranch Report), 1972-09 (Box 5)
- Cornell in the Seventies - Goals, Prioritues and Plans, 1973-04 (Box 5)
- Endowed Ithaca - Capital Needs and Resources 1977-78 Plans, 1977-09 (Box 5)
  The first Capital Budget System at Ithaca (J. W. Rudan project)
- Some Thoughts on Managing Decline (W. R. Lynn), 1977-10 (Box 5)
- CBORD Dining, 1975-1980 (Box 5)
- National Planning Data Corp, 1969-1981 (Box 5)
- Systems Programming Issues (R D Cowles), 1979 (Box 5)
- Graphs, Real Money Allocations, Production/No. Jobs, Worksheets, Recovery Rates, 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Agenda, 1968-06-1970-06 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Directors Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- OCS Reports, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Fact Books (Endowed and Statutory), 1980-11 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Cornell Indicators, 1976-1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Envelope of Photographs - Project Ezra Fair (Jon Crispin), 1987 (Box 7)
- Envelope of Photographs Project Ezra participants from CU and IBM (Box 7)
  (noted as Photographs Archives)
- Photographs or early Micro installations and PC sales office (Box 7)
- Envelope with Slides: CR's Talk, Slides: AEP, San Diego CA (2 packs), 1986 (Box 7)
  - Cornell Slides, Cornell Reunion Slides, 1986-06
- Project Ezra Goals of Project Ezra, 1988-12 (Box 7)
- Project Ezra Projects Funded, 1988-12 (Box 7)
- Project Ezra Participants, 1988-12 (Box 7)
- Project Ezra Setting up Hardware and Software (Box 7)
- Project Ezra: (by college) Engineering, Graduate School of Management, Hotel, Human Ecology, Industrial and Labor Relations, Law School, Medical School, Ornithology, Vet School, Architecture, Art, and Planning, Agriculture, Arts and Sciences, Biology, CCS, CISER (Box 7)
- Photographs - Geri Gay's First Videodisk with DMLL/German (Box 7)
- Project Ezra - Correspondence, reports, proposals, etc, 1985-1988 (Box 7)
- Cornell Engineer (article on Project Ezra), 1987-02-1987-03 (Box 7)
- Academic Computing at Cornell (Focus on Project Ezra), 1985 (Box 7)
  Winter
- Project Ezra Fair: Tools for Learning, 1986-03, 1987-05 (Box 7)
- Project Ezra - Listing of Coordinators and Participants, 1988-01 (Box 7)
- Project Ezra: Listing of Archive contents (Pickup Report), 1987-12 (Box 7)
- Attachments A's (equipment lists and shipping dates), 1986-1989 (Box 7)
- Project Ezra: Final Totals and Participants, 1988-12 (Box 7)
- Project Ezra - Lunchtime Bytes, Fairs, AEP Conf, etc (Box 7)
- Project Ezra Newsletters, 1986-1988 (Box 7)
- Project Ezra: Liaison Status Summaries, 1985 (Box 7)
- Payroll/Personnel Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 8)
- Geocode Update, 1978 (Box 8)
- Area/Class Report Changes, 1978 (Box 8)
- Personnel Data Project Systems, 1979 (Box 8)
- Hardware, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
- IBM Series I, 1979 (Box 8)
- Telephone Company Responses, 1979 (Box 8)
- SDPP 1-4, 1979 (Box 8)
- Administrative Programming Service Requests, 1979 (Box 8)
- Affirmative Action Advisory Board, 1979 (Box 8)
- Availability Statistics, 1977-1979 (Box 8)
- Bursar Users Meetings, 1979 (Box 8)
- 3350 Conversion Group Meeting, 1979 (Box 8)
- APS Income Projections, 1979 (Box 8)
- Major Installation, 1978-1980 (Box 8)
- OCS Systems Projects, 1979 (Box 8)
- PA Parents Updating Process, 1979 (Box 8)
- MSA Maintenance Problem Status Reports, 1976-1979 (Box 8)
- APS Staff Activity, 1979-1980 (Box 8)
- Systems Files, 1970-1979 (Box 8)
- Systems Files, 1976 (Box 8)
- Computer Services: Administrative Prod Units Activity Report, 1978-07-1978-12 (Box 8)
  (blank account setup request forms)
- Mass Storage System: VM/370, 1977 (Box 8)
- Minidisk Manager - General Spec, 1977 (Box 8)
- Minidisk Manager Implementation - Goals and Approach, 1977-1978 (Box 8)
- Minidisk Manager - Implementation Spec: OS MD support in CMS, 1978 (Box 8)
- OCS Acquisition of the IBM 3850 MSS, 1977 (Box 8)
- Using the VS! Assembler under OS, 1977 (Box 8)
- TZT profile, relink everything in RR, 1977 (Box 8)
- Staff for MSS Project, 1978 (Box 8)
- HASP, Spool and Queue Design Session, 1978 (Box 8)
- Tymnet Interface Guide, 1977 (Box 8)
- VM Project for use in presentation to IBM, 1977 (Box 8)
- CUMC and OCS Proposal, 1977 (Box 8)
- Use of Favoring for Virtual Machines, 1977 (Box 8)
- Sys. Utilization Monitor, 1977 (Box 8)
- Per Under VM/370, 1977 (Box 8)
- IBM Presentation at Share 48, 1977 (Box 8)
- OS/VS1 Extended Control Program, 1977 (Box 8)
- Tymnet Subscriber Directory, 1977 (Box 8)
- XFOR-80 Fort IC Cross Assembler for the Z80, 1977 (Box 8)
- Minidisk for Sharing Systems Prog, 1977 (Box 8)
- Innovation Data Processing, 1977 (Box 8)
- Decimal/Hexidecimal Arithmetic Conversion, 1977 (Box 8)
- Prop Plan for Regoranizing subset S-disk, 1977 (Box 8)
- System Utilization Monitor Design Specs, 1977 (Box 8)
- VM User Modification Library, 1977 (Box 8)
- VM User Modification Library, 1976-05 (Box 8)
- VS1 Considerations, 1975 (Box 8)
- Host Interface Specification, 1975 (Box 8)
- The Yorktown Research Batch System, 1975 (Box 8)
- Anatomy of a Spy, 1975 (Box 8)
- MVT/360 Users Guide, 1972 (Box 8)
- Intro to OS/360 MVT Control Logic and Debugging w Core Dumps (2), 1969 (Box 8)
- ACOS File System Program Logic (Box 8)
- Appointments and Assignments in Systems Facilities, 1977 (Box 8)
- OS Dataset Incremental Backup and Recovery (Migration), 1977 (Box 8)
- Care and Feeding of the FSTask, 1977 (Box 8)
- Setup and VM Link documentation, 1977 (Box 8)
- (SUM) internals/externals, 1977 (Box 8)
- Running a Virtual OS, 1977 (Box 8)
- (SUM) data, 1977 (Box 8)
- IBM Support/IBM Products, 1976 (Box 8)
- Prop. Doc and Coding Standards for NBER, 1976 (Box 8)
- Standards for VM Rel 3, 1976 (Box 8)
- Proclib cleanup, 1976 (Box 8)
- Test Time Reorgan Proposal, 1976 (Box 8)
- Performance Measurement of the 3 and 4 Megabyte 370/168, 1977 (Box 8)
- Systems Group Organization, 1977 (Box 8)
- Space considerations, 1988 (Box 9)
- Maple Avenue Renovation Project, 1994-1995 (Box 9)
- Building Supercomputing AIX, 1990 (Box 9)
  Experiences with PAIX (documents and overheads)
- AIX- SuperAIX Share/Supeur overheads, 1990 (Box 9)
- Program for SUPEUR Supercomputing in Europe - Meeting, 1991 (Box 9)
  Fall
- Information Technologies at Cornell, 1990-07 (Box 9)
  Presentation to IBM ACIS
- Verville - IBM SuperAIX/MSS, 1991-09 (Box 9)
- Mexico City - Networking at CU - Master docs and overheads, 1992-11 (Box 9)
- Mexico City - Computing at CU - Master docs and overheads, 1992-11 (Box 9)
- Mexico City - Arrangements, etc, 1992-11 (Box 9)
- CIT Presentation to Visitors from Brazil (docs and overheads), 1993-07 (Box 9)
- Rio de Janeiro, Brazil/ IBM - Arrangements, etc, 1992-08 (Box 9)
- Rio de Janeiro, Brazil/ IBM - Networking Handouts, 1992-08 (Box 9)
- La Hulpe, Belgium/IBM Europe - Computing at Cornell (J W Rudan), 1992-02 (Box 9)
  Documents and Overheads
- New Tools for Supercomputing (J W Rudan), 1992-10 (Box 9)
  Presentation at IT Executive Conference, La Hulpe, Belgium
- Briefings to visitors from Brazil (Supercomputing/CIT), 1994-04-1994-08 (Box 9)
- CR Team Organization - Foils for IR Quarterly Review, 1993-04 (Box 9)
- CAUCAS - Conference Program Fayetteville, Ark, 1994-04 (Box 9)
- Functional Area Reports (monthly), 1994-1995 (Box 9)
- Adopting a Rapid Application Development Methodology (Koehler), 1992 (Box 9)
- IVY+ assorted materials, meetings, copies of members, policies, etc, 1987-1993 (Box 9)
- IVY+ at CAUSE '94, 1994 (Box 9)
- IR Team Management, 1993-1995 (Box 9)
- CU Central Systems Security Audit Report and Auditor/Audit Risk Analysis Project, 1994-1995 (Box 9)
- EPD Audit, 1994-1995 (Box 9)
- Exemplar, 1994 (Box 9)
- Fred Roger's Hyperion Funding, 1994 (Box 9)
- OSF, 1991 (Box 9)
- ADSPAC Planning Meeting, 1993 (Box 9)
- Information Tech. Strategic Planning Meetings, 1993 (Box 9)
- TRG 2 folders, 1995 (Box 9)
- TRG: Institutional Advancement IAN Plan, 1995 (Box 9)
- SKILLSET Folder, 1995 (Box 9)
- Art Matrix - Homer Smith materials, 1990 (Box 10)
- Projects and Committee Reports (Box 10)
  - Internal Information Dissemination, 1989-1990
  - Technologies Committee, 1991
  - XA Conversion, 1987-1988
  - Services Committee, 1989-1991
  - Bear Access, 1992
  - Text Systems Plan, 1981
  - Electronic Mail, 1988
  - Terminal Emulation, 1988
  - Progress Toward Diversity, 1991-05
    (Annual Report of Status of Women and Minorities)
  - CIT Logo Project - different proposals and final, 1989-07
  - CIT Alert Templates, 1989
  - CIT Briefly: Template for News Briefs from CIT, 1989
  - CIT Covers, 1989
    Workstation (Personal Computer) Ownership Among Freshman and Sophomores 1990, Freshmen, Sophomores, and Juniors 1991, Undergraduates at Cornell 1993, Students at Cornell 1994, Undergraduates at Cornell 1994 and 1995, Faculty, Lecturers, and Staff at Cornell 1993
- Proposal for Flexible Lease/Rental, 1991 (Box 10)
- CIT Focus Projects - Project Planning, 1989 (Box 10)
- Project Mandarin, 1991 (Box 10)
- Project Mandarin (project documents), 1993-03 (Box 10)
- Project Mandarin (CIT Published material), 1993-12 (Box 10)
- Project Mandarin and the World Wide Web, 1995-07 (Box 10)
- Project Mandarin Consortium, 1994 (Box 10)
- Project Mandarin Consortium Bylaws/Legal Issues, 1994-1995 (Box 10)
- Project Mandarin Consortium EBG Meeting, 1995-03 (Box 10)
- Project Mandarin Consortium License Agreement, 1995 (Box 10)
- Project Mandarin Consortium Services Agreement, 1995 (Box 10)
- Project Mandarin Consortium Transfer Agreement, 1995 (Box 10)
- Computer Network Pilot Project, 1991 (Box 10)
- Technology in Science Education, 1979 (Box 10)
  (The Next Ten Years)
- Using Software: CCS Guide, 1987 (Box 10)
- Planning for Learning Technologies Services, 1995 (Box 10)
  (report by FABIT)
- An Introduction to Information Tech. at Cornell, 1990 (Box 10)
- Statistical Computing for Research (2 copies), 1990 (Box 10)
- Windows Project, 1988 (Box 10)
- Videodisc Fair, 1986 (Box 10)
- Special Projects/Organization Chart, 1986 (Box 10)
- Project Milestone, 1984 (Box 10)
- Word Processing for Humanists, 1981-1982 (Box 10)
- Coopers and Lybrand - Proposal to Develop a Comprehensive, 1995-08 (Box 10)
  Administrative. Improvement Plan
- CU Final Reports by IBM Consulting Services, 1995-10 (Box 10)
- IBM/Cornell Partnership in Information Systems, 1995 (Box 10)
- Proposal to Atlantic Philanthropy for Project 2000 Support (Box 10)
- Sponsored Projects Systems, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
- IVY+ at CAUSE 97, 1997 (Box 11)
- P2K Steering Group, 1996 (Box 11)
- Delta Team and Finance Division (2 files), 1995 (Box 11)
- IR Management and Mgmt Team Meetings (3 folders), 1995-1996 (Box 11)
- IR Income and Estimates, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
- P2K Steering Group, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
- P2K: Project Definition Report by IBM, 1996-09 (Box 11)
- P2K Project Control Book by IBM, 1996-09 (Box 11)
- P2K Miscellaneous (2 folders), 1995 (Box 11)
- Data Warehousing, 1995 (Box 11)
- APS Organization, 1973-1990 (Box 11)
- The GLOB (of JSOstrom) printout, 1983 (Box 11)
- The GLOB (JWR original plans), 1980-1989 (Box 11)
- The GLOB, 1993-1996 (Box 11)
- CIT Financial Restructuring - status report, reporting system (GLOB), 1990 (Box 11)
- CIT: CR Status/Quarterly Report, 1990 (Box 11)
- CIT Priorities, 1990-1991 (Box 11)
- Distributed Computing and VM/ESA Environments (Bob Cowles), 1992-07 (Box 11)
- A Systems Programming View of AIX/370, 1991-02 (Box 11)
  The Cornell Experience
- Server Farm Billing Rates, 1993 (Box 11)
- An Introduction to Info Tech at Cornell (publication), 1989 (Box 11)
- Apple Corporate Visit, 1989 (Box 11)
- Corporate Visit to Apple, 1994 (Box 11)
- QIP Ethnic Codes Study, 1994 (Box 11)
- XEROX, 1994 (Box 11)
- CIT - Perspectives for Employees, 1989 (Box 11)
- IVY +, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
- CIT Staff Training and Customer Service, 1991 (Box 11)
- Legendary Service Game Plan, 1991 (Box 11)
- Service Lists, 1990-05 (Box 11)
- Cornell A/C machines - Users and Package use, 1990-07-1990-09 (Box 11)
- CIT Outreach Initiative, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
- CIT Sr Mgmt Meeting Minutes ( Action Logs/initial Mandarin), 1988-1989 (Box 11)
- CIT Sr Mgmt Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 11)
- CIT Sr Mgmt Meeting Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
- Budget and Budget Office Issues (Tom Cardman), 1985-1987 (Box 11)
- Budget and Budget Office Issues (Tom Cardman), 1987-1988 (Box 11)
- IBM IX/370 UNIX, 1985-10 (Box 12)
  System V Joint Study - Final Reports
- IBM Mainframe Folder, 1991 (Box 12)
- Miscellaneous Contracts, 1981-1987 (Box 12)
- Adesse Corp Page Migration Contract, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Scheduler Contract Holders, 1982-1983
    (Univ of Rochester, Adesse Corp, Universitair Rekencentrum)
- Minidisk Manager (MDM) Contract Holders (Box 12)
  MDMComputer Associates, Univ. Nijmegen, Netherlands, Univ. of Ottawa, Univ. of Rochester, Texas A and M, Univ. of Waterloo, Yale, Weizmann Inst of Science, Israeil, Univesitat Zurich-Irchel, Switzerland.
- CIT/MSL Memorandums, 1988 (Box 12)
- Editing Notes, 1981 (Box 12)
- NetComm Request for Services, 1989 (Box 12)
- CCS Hardware Meeting Notes (w Chris McMahon from IBM), 1988 (Box 12)
- Page Migration Requests, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
- VM/SP Enhanced Page Migration Adesse Products, 1980 (Box 12)
- Cornell Page Migration, 1981 (Box 12)
- Cornell 3805 Page Migration, 1982 (Box 12)
- IX/370 (Box 12)
  - 3103 Disposition, 1981-1983
  - Contracts, Budgeting, Non-Disclosure Agreements, Misc., 1985